I'd like to, we have about half an hour
then, so our friends have to leave, we're going
to cry for you.
You told me 9:00 to 9:45, even though
we have 15 minutes to finish. I
can do
the stress, I can do it.
We already finished three chapters, half of them. I haven't
forgotten that I owe you one and a
half more chapters. Don't worry, I haven't forgotten.
If we did it correctly, then I'm going to
show you the first
minute of a video that can start
the project.
First chapter, we studied the Paris
of Indians,
the red one, and the object, something very beautiful that
I like a lot. Let's
see
[Music]
and clearly,
and I learned that principle in science,
that there is a problem, like how light comes
from the sun to the earth, and there is a problem.
Steven Hawking couldn't solve it, but
we solved it because here's
the problem, it's in this. I'm not going to
show you the whole video.
It's Nagarjuna
and
[Music]
well
x 2
and and
very good
today
[Music]
but not to play
same
for
[Music]
you are
tome
and that this doesn't have  Sense
and quantum science, we don't know how the
sun touches the earth. We would die in the sun, we would
n't have food, we wouldn't have the sun
to tan us. How can it come from the sun? We don't
know how it comes from the sun.
This is chapter 3. He's talking
about chapter 3, how it comes from the sun. This
light,
the fasts, it opens, it
comes from my mind and it's creating
the sun and in myself.
How the sunlight comes to this earth
is a seed that opens in your mind.
How does the food grow from this light?
Today is about chapter 32, chapter 4,
what was
the beagle examination in Sanskrit, of a
couple, of a
standard, examining the five parts
of a person. So for this
weekend, what's weird about the
elements, with the results of the
elements,
is that aspirin
has chemicals
inside.
[Music]
Our mom tells us, like my mom
told me, I only get really bad
headaches when I was a kid.
Months later, just take an aspirin. And
I remember one day nothing happened. I remember
a bed I was in. I couldn't
even go to my room. I was in my
half brother's bed. Nothing happened. It did
n't work.
I have a headache, my daughter takes the
second one, 10 minutes
later
I need to sweat, she told me she grabbed
the little bottle and said for children it's
only two, she told me sorry you can't have another one, I
said but mommy I'll give you more for your
head and she told me
something very very bad, sometimes you just have to have a
headache and I said
then we before always
believed it up our mom not there, she said
sometimes aspirin works and sometimes
aspirin doesn't work, okay dear, that's how
life is, she lied to me, a
plumber,
she didn't tell me the truth, she didn't
understand chapter 4 of refusing one,
she believed
at 22 to Carlos
in the aspirin molecule, she believed
that the aspiring neonate very special and
special molecule, she believed it,
the second example of chapter 4
we have no real medical example
which in chapter 3 in the sunlight
as it touches the earth with chapter 4
aspirin, which is chapter 5
space in the definition of
maxillary space and the action, '
fire stays in the hot, nobody
took the hot inside the fire there is
Something that's inside is
chapter five and the fire,
the heat of friendly fire, which is a
practice, what is the practice, the practical thing we
can use to throw it in New
York, and after my three-year retreat
is to teach the 18 courses in Galicia, and
then I made an announcement and told them I'm
going to New York, everything was like, I
remember my students, I told them I don't have any
rope, New York, I'm going to
do a three-year retreat,
a vision, a little one, where I was
crying with the lion,
one more talk at the World Trade Center
in New York, and this talk and I told them,
oh,
the metal of this building has the
action, it's hard, it's hard and it can
hold up this building so big, what
is holding up the World Trade
Center is this metal already inside, and it has
the scene, it has something hard, it has this, it has
hardness and strength, right? Not
that strength and hardness when I remember
that I gave them to New York, the last thing I
did is
not the thick,
the hardness in the strength within the state,
even the mental strength and hardness, which is what is
making you, in
fact, hold up, it's the
walls, it's your karma,
its seeds, they are, they are not the
Bricks, don't think like that if you want to
eat Ingush, actually, over your head you
want to be in an apartment and
you want a place to live, you need to
do it, he's halfway through in 113
steps and he's giving other people a
place to stay and if not, that building is going to fall down.
What happens? I
went to the three-year retreat, you remember there were so
many military planes, so
many planes practicing, and
we were like, we're not here and
we say, what's happening here? I didn't know
if we left the retreat, then the newspaper arrived,
Astrid Perez,
people
[Music]
something that starts to scream and put them,
starts to scream things. I imagine
today a churro in the garden and what
happens when you feel stressed at home? You eat a
lot, that's why we get fat from so
much stress. That's how a magician is when they
go to his house at night with me, 33 plates,
or would it be because I'm tired
too? The wife, thinkers, speeches, it's
not for me, I have to grab something
to feel happy,
the churro is going to make me happy. Listen,
Nagarjuna doesn't like surfing
and he asks what part of the... I'll...
the first one as soon as...  It touches as soon as it touches
the tongue if this is done in front of the
churro that is with which the front
of the churro that touches the tongue and that is
the rest of chapter 6
sugar the sugar the sugar crystal its
face no sugar never touches the tongue
if it did touch it
of counting they cannot touch so they
touch
a little bit of sugar will have to
become a little bit on the
tongue
sometimes the sugar has to
become on the tongue and it is not possible
but if the sugar becomes on the
tongue then they could not affect
each other understand the sugar and you
can give a taste to the tongue if
they get mixed up then the poop would
also give its taste to the wings on
the tongue because also I don't know
there is a house there is a house of a little
special that game what will give you will
give you a scare because the sugar has
seen it as the sugar is in my mouth no no it
is so much a tongue does not touch it because if it did
not touch they would mix in
store so that the leaves of good taste
when you are stressed the sugar would give it there
should be a little mix they would
mix
the same rich taste so it wants  To
say that everything that doesn't mix with
the tongue should give you a good
taste, or if it does mix with the tongue it
should turn into sugars, is not
possible. It's the same as the professor in
the video. I don't know what's going on.
Is it possible that the wife could feel
better by eating the churro? It's
not possible, it's impossible. Last
question: wife, do they have to go and Tim
has to be an ad? Maybe because
things always feel
worse after the husband gets angry and
leaves. If she eats churros, why does she
eat three plates and it would be the
night? Because she wants to eat,
she does need to feel relaxed,
comforted. The positions are wet, she
needs it,
so the churro gives her the sweet taste,
the comfort churro. Then she
went past number three in the
English one.
With that karma, it comes to you through the
churro. Do you understand? And then you don't eat
the churro, well, you'll be thin and you can
feel good about your husband. That's
how we use the four chapters. Use them in
our day. Use them on Tumblr.
13 steps. They got
married this morning, so what?